IMBAULT Kenji

★ kenjiimbault@gmail.com

• 10 Chemin du Bassin, 13014 Marseille

https://kenjiimbault.github.io/personal-website/

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/kenjiimbault/

+33 7 83 14 41 64

Driver's License

https://github.com/KenjiImbault

Carpentras, France

2020 - 2021

2018 - 2019

2001-04-04

Profile

Engineering student specialized in Industrial Engineering. Worked in a team, both professionally and during my studies. Also able to work independently, as demonstrated in multiple personal projects. Excited to apply the theoretical knowledge learned to real-world challenges, and to learn more in the field.

Education

Master of Science in Industrial Engineering and IT Polytech Marseille ☑	2021 – 2024 Marseille, France
Higher School Preparatory Classes in Technology and Industrial Sciences High school Jean-Baptiste Dumas ☑	2019 – 2021 Alès, France
Bachelor of Science and Technology in Industry and Sustainable Development	2017 – 2019

Professional Experiences

High school Jean Henri Fabre □

Implementation of a machine simulator for a digital infrastructure2023-06 - 2023-08Fraunhofer Innovation Platform for Advanced Manufacturing ☑Enschede,Created and implemented a machine simulator OPC UA server in C# to create a digital twin ofThe Netherlands

a shop floor Created the game logic of the Unity model of the shop floor

Shelf stacking2022-06 – 2022-08E. Leclerc □Carpentras, France

Projects

Beer Distribution Game	2022 – 2023
Wanted to a taken of the male a Dana Distribution Course in Java Coulet	

Worked in a team of 5 to make a Beer Distribution Game in JavaScript

Role: Programmer

Motorized bench for tensioning paraglider ropes

Worked in a team of 4 to make a bench to tension the ropes of a paraglider

Role: Project Manager - Programmer

Mechanical study of an exoskeleton

Technical Skills

Python (Sympy, numpy...) | MATLAB (MATLAB, Simulink...) | C# | HTML & CSS | SQL | OPCUA

Operating Systems (Windows, Linux, Android)

Other skills

Control theory | PLCs (Ladder diagram, GRAFCET) | Scheduling | Project management

Quality management | Financial accounting

Languages

French (Native) | English (TOEIC, C1)

Certificates

Driver's License | Zyxel ZCNP Foundation - v1.0 EN ☑ | Zyxel ZCNP Security - v1.0 EN ☑ | TOEIC (975/990)

Interests

Aikido (Practised Aikido for +6 years in a club) | **Running** (Trail running for 1 year)